[
  {
    "question": "Alabama",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Montgomery",
      "wrongOne": "Birmingham",
      "wrongTwo": "Mobile",
      "wrongThree": "Huntsville"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Alaska",
    "answers": {    
      "correct": "Juneau",
      "wrongOne": "Anchorage",
      "wrongTwo": "Fairbanks",
      "wrongThree": "Sitka"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Arkansas",
    "answers": {    
      "correct": "Phoenix",
      "wrongOne": "Tucson",
      "wrongTwo": "Mesa",
      "wrongThree": "Glendale"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Alabama",
    "answers": {    
      "correct": "Little Rock",
      "wrongOne": "Fort Smith",
      "wrongTwo": "Fayetteville",
      "wrongThree": "Springdale"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "California",
    "answers": {    
      "correct": "Sacramento",
      "wrongOne": "San Diego",
      "wrongTwo": "Los Angeles",
      "wrongThree": "San Francisco"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Colorado",
    "answers": {    
      "correct": "Denver",
      "wrongOne": "Colorado Springs",
      "wrongTwo": "Aurora",
      "wrongThree": "Fort Collins"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Connecticut",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Hartford",
      "wrongOne": "New Haven",
      "wrongTwo": "Stamford",
      "wrongThree": "Bridgeport"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Delaware",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Dover",
      "wrongOne": "Wilmington",
      "wrongTwo": "Newark",
      "wrongThree": "Middletown"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Florida",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Tallahassee",
      "wrongOne": "Miami",
      "wrongTwo": "Jacksonville",
      "wrongThree": "Orlando"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Georgia",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Atlanta",
      "wrongOne": "Columbus",
      "wrongTwo": "Augusta",
      "wrongThree": "Savannah"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Hawaii",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Honolulu",
      "wrongOne": "Hilo",
      "wrongTwo": "Kailua",
      "wrongThree": "Kapolei"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Idaho",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Boise",
      "wrongOne": "Nampa",
      "wrongTwo": "Meridian",
      "wrongThree": "Idaho Falls"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Illinois",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Springfield",
      "wrongOne": "Aurora",
      "wrongTwo": "Rockford",
      "wrongThree": "Chicago"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Indiana",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Indianapolis",
      "wrongOne": "Fort Wayne",
      "wrongTwo": "Evansville",
      "wrongThree": "Gary"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Iowa",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Des Moines",
      "wrongOne": "Cedar Rapids",
      "wrongTwo": "Davenport",
      "wrongThree": "Sioux City"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Kansas",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Topeka",
      "wrongOne": "Overland Park",
      "wrongTwo": "Kansas City",
      "wrongThree": "Wichita"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Kentucky",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Frankfort",
      "wrongOne": "Lexington",
      "wrongTwo": "Bowling Green",
      "wrongThree": "Louisville"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Louisiana",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Baton Rouge",
      "wrongOne": "New Orleans",
      "wrongTwo": "Shreveport",
      "wrongThree": "Lafayette"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Maine",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Augusta",
      "wrongOne": "Lewiston",
      "wrongTwo": "Bangor",
      "wrongThree": "Portland"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Maryland",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Annapolis",
      "wrongOne": "Columbia",
      "wrongTwo": "Baltimore",
      "wrongThree": "Silver Spring"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Boston",
      "wrongOne": "Worcester",
      "wrongTwo": "Springfield",
      "wrongThree": "Cambridge"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Michigan",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Lansing",
      "wrongOne": "Grand Rapids",
      "wrongTwo": "Detroit",
      "wrongThree": "Ann Arbor"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Minnesota",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Saint Paul",
      "wrongOne": "Minneapolis",
      "wrongTwo": "Rochester",
      "wrongThree": "Bloomington"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Mississippi",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Jackson",
      "wrongOne": "Gulfport",
      "wrongTwo": "Southaven",
      "wrongThree": "Biloxi"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Missouri",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Jefferson City",
      "wrongOne": "Saint Louis",
      "wrongTwo": "Springfield",
      "wrongThree": "Kansas City"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Montana",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Helena",
      "wrongOne": "Missoula",
      "wrongTwo": "Great Falls",
      "wrongThree": "Billings"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Nebraska",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Lincoln",
      "wrongOne": "Omaha",
      "wrongTwo": "Bellevue",
      "wrongThree": "Grand Island"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Nevada",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Carson City",
      "wrongOne": "Henderson",
      "wrongTwo": "Reno",
      "wrongThree": "Las Vegas"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "New Hampshire",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Concord",
      "wrongOne": "Nashua",
      "wrongTwo": "Manchester",
      "wrongThree": "Rochester"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "New Jersey",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Trenton",
      "wrongOne": "Jersey City",
      "wrongTwo": "Newark",
      "wrongThree": "Paterson"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "New Mexico",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Santa Fe",
      "wrongOne": "Las Cruces",
      "wrongTwo": "Rio Rancho",
      "wrongThree": "Albuquerque"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "New York",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Albany",
      "wrongOne": "Buffalo",
      "wrongTwo": "Rochester",
      "wrongThree": "New York City"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "North Carolina",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Raleigh",
      "wrongOne": "Charlotte",
      "wrongTwo": "Greensboro",
      "wrongThree": "Durham"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "North Dakota",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Bismarck",
      "wrongOne": "Fargo",
      "wrongTwo": "Grand Forks",
      "wrongThree": "Minot"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Ohio",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Columbus",
      "wrongOne": "Cleveland",
      "wrongTwo": "Cincinnati",
      "wrongThree": "Toledo"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Oklahoma",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Oklahoma City",
      "wrongOne": "Tulsa",
      "wrongTwo": "Norman",
      "wrongThree": "Broken Arrow"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Oregon",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Salem",
      "wrongOne": "Portland",
      "wrongTwo": "Eugene",
      "wrongThree": "Gresham"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Pennsylvania",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Harrisburg",
      "wrongOne": "Pittsburgh",
      "wrongTwo": "Allentown",
      "wrongThree": "Philadelphia"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Rhode Island",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Providence",
      "wrongOne": "Warwick",
      "wrongTwo": "Cranston",
      "wrongThree": "Pawtucket"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "South Carolina",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Columbia",
      "wrongOne": "Charleston",
      "wrongTwo": "North Charleston",
      "wrongThree": "Mount Pleasant"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "South Dakota",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Pierre",
      "wrongOne": "Rapid City",
      "wrongTwo": "Aberdeen",
      "wrongThree": "Sioux Falls"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Tennessee",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Nashville",
      "wrongOne": "Memphis",
      "wrongTwo": "Knoxville",
      "wrongThree": "Chattanooga"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Texas",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Austin",
      "wrongOne": "San Antonio",
      "wrongTwo": "Dallas",
      "wrongThree": "Houston"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Utah",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Salt Lake City",
      "wrongOne": "West Valley City",
      "wrongTwo": "Provo",
      "wrongThree": "West Jordan"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Vermont",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Montpelier",
      "wrongOne": "Essex",
      "wrongTwo": "Burlington",
      "wrongThree": "Colchester"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Virginia",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Richmond",
      "wrongOne": "Norfolk",
      "wrongTwo": "Virginia Beach",
      "wrongThree": "Arlington"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Washington",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Olympia",
      "wrongOne": "Spokane",
      "wrongTwo": "Tacoma",
      "wrongThree": "Seattle"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "West Virginia",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Charleston",
      "wrongOne": "Huntington",
      "wrongTwo": "Parkersburg",
      "wrongThree": "Morgantown"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Wisconsin",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Madison",
      "wrongOne": "Milwaukee",
      "wrongTwo": "Green Bay",
      "wrongThree": "Kenosha"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Wyoming",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Cheyenne",
      "wrongOne": "Casper",
      "wrongTwo": "Laramie",
      "wrongThree": "Gillette"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "the United States of America",
    "answers": {
      "correct": "Washington D.C.",
      "wrongOne": "New York",
      "wrongTwo": "Chicago",
      "wrongThree": "Philadelphia"
      }
  }
]